SCIMA-300  

ASSIGNMENT 3 - DATA COMPARISON


In the final assignment I have attempted to draw comparison between my previous two assignments. The first assignment was “Digital Data Selfie” in which I recorded 72 hrs of digital communication and organized them in spreadsheet. In the second assignment I recorded analog communications for a 24 hour time period. 

The final assignment presents two sets of data, first set of data is a comparison between the first two assignment in terms of the type of message sent and the type of conversation had. It compares the information to the time of the day. Showing the viewer the type of mood I have at what time of the day. 

The second set of data presents the gestures expressed by the sender and the assumptions I made/or make about the gestures expressed by my receiver. Its an attempt to show how fake we can be when we are behind a screen and how things change when we come face to face. 

Hope you like it!

Thank you,
Nitisha
